saletab.com 2013-10-06

# Privacy Policy

**Saletab.com Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Saletab.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.saletab.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Saletab.com.

**Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate: name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us.

Users may however visit our Site anonymously. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal Identification Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider utilized and other similar information.

**Web Browser Cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How Do We Use Collected Information**

Saletab.com collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To personalize user experience_

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

  *   _To improve customer service_

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

  *   _To process transactions_

We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

  *   _To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature_

To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

  *   _To send periodic emails_

The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How Do We Protect Your Information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username,

Password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third Party Websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Saletab.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Terms and Conditions of Use**

If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Saletab.com’s relationship with you in relation to this website.

The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

1\. The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without prior notice.

2\. Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.

3\. Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.

4\. This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.

5\. All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.

6\. Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.

7\. From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).

8\. You may not create a link to this website from another website or document without Saletab.com’s prior written consent.

9\. Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of Saudi Arabia.

**Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [help@saletab.com](mailto:help@saletab.com) .

**Offices:**

_**United States**_

11701 Hickman Mills Dr 

Kansas City 

Kansas 64134 

United States

Tel: 1 816 256 8284

_**Bahrain**_

Office 111, Dream Tower Building No. 1, Building 474, Road 1010, Block 410

Sanabis Area

Kingdom of Bahrain

Tel: 973 17007253

_**China**_

Room 1501,Block C,HeQiao building,No.8 GuangHua Road,ChaoYang District,Beijing,China/北京市朝阳区光华路甲8号和乔大厦C座1501  
P.C.:100026  
Tel:86-10-51249171  
Fax:86-10-65815508

_**Saudi Arabia**_

3rd Floor Al Mulhim Tower  
Mubaraz, Al Ahsa  
31982  
Saudi Arabia  
Tel: 966 3 5622644
